videowhisper.com 2017-11-29

# Privacy Policy - Webcam Site Plugins for Video Streaming, Chat, Conference, Recording, Presentation

By using the VideoWhisper.com Service, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this notice.

This Privacy Policy applies to VideoWhisper.com’s collection and use of your personal information (i.e., information that identifies a specific person, such as full name or email address). It also describes generally VideoWhisper.com’s practices for handling non-personal information (for example, interests, demographics and services usage).

Your use of the VideoWhisper.com Service and any personal information you provide through the VideoWhisper.com Service are subject at all times to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.

**Cookie policy**

VideoWhisper.com (with its affiliates) uses certain technologies on its network of websites, software applications, or any other products offered by VideoWhisper.com (the “VideoWhisper.com Services”) to collect information that helps us improve your online experience. In this Cookie Policy, we refer to these technologies, which include cookies, pixels, web beacons, and gifs, collectively as “cookies.” This policy explains the different types of cookies used on the VideoWhisper.com Services and how you can control them. We may change this Cookie Policy at any time: please take a look at the “last modified” legend at the top of this page to see when this Cookie Policy was last revised. Any changes in this Cookie Policy will become effective when we make the revised Cookie Policy available on or through the VideoWhisper.com Services.

By agreeing to this Cookie Policy, or by using the VideoWhisper.com Services or any service of ours that links to this Cookie Policy, you expressly consent to information handling practices and storage and access of cookies as described in this policy.

We hope that this policy helps you understand, and feel more confident about, our use of cookies. If you have any further queries, please contact us using contact page from VideoWhisper.com .

**The Information VideoWhisper.com Collects**

Information You Provide: You may provide to VideoWhisper.com what is generally called "personally identifiable" information (such as your name, email address, credit card number, postal mailing address, and telephone numbers) if you use certain services or products from the VideoWhisper.com Service, enter contests or sweepstakes, or otherwise use the features and functionality of the VideoWhisper.com Service.

“Automatically Collected“ Information: When you access the VideoWhisper.com Service (including through your computer or your mobile device) or open one of our HTML emails, we may automatically record certain information from our system by using different types of tracking technology. This “automatically collected“ information may include Internet Protocol address ("IP Address"), a unique user ID, version of software installed, system type, the content and pages that you access on the VideoWhisper.com Service, and the dates and times that you visit the VideoWhisper.com Service.

“Cookies“ Information: When you access the VideoWhisper.com Service, we may send one or more cookies . small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters . to your computer. VideoWhisper.com may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the VideoWhisper.com Service. Persistent cookies can be removed. Please review your web browser "Help" file to learn the best way to modify your cookie settings.

“Pixel Tags“ or “Clear Gifs“ A pixel tag, also known as a clear GIF or web beacon, is an invisible tag placed on certain pages of our VideoWhisper.com Service but not on your computer. When you access these pages, pixel tags generate a generic notice of that visit. They usually work in conjunction with cookies, registering when a particular computer visits a particular page. If you turn off cookies the pixel tag will simply detect an anonymous website visit.

Your User ID. Your User ID is displayed throughout the VideoWhisper.com Service and is therefore available to the public. Other people can see your feedback, ratings and associated comments, etc. Therefore, if you associate your actual name with your User ID, the people to whom you have revealed your name will be able to personally identify your activities on the VideoWhisper.com Service.

**The Way VideoWhisper.com Uses Information**

VideoWhisper.com uses the information that you provide or that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide all of the features and services found on the VideoWhisper.com Service as well as to track user-generated content and Users to the extent necessary to comply as a service provider with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act and other applicable laws.

We may use your email address or mobile number, without further consent, for administrative communications such as notifying you of major VideoWhisper.com Service updates, for customer service purposes, and to send privacy or security related notices.

VideoWhisper.com uses all of the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of our Users, to improve the way the VideoWhisper.com Service works and looks, to create new features and functionality.

VideoWhisper.com may use .Automatically Collected. information and .Cookies. information to: (a) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you access the VideoWhisper.com Service; (b) provide customized third-party advertisements, content and information; (c) monitor and report on the effectiveness of third-party marketing campaigns; (d) monitor and report aggregate usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages accessed; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions or other activities.

**Information Disclosure**

VideoWhisper.com does not share your personally identifiable information with other organizations for their marketing or promotional uses without your prior express consent. Please be aware, however, that any personally identifiable information that you voluntarily choose to display on any publicly available portion of the VideoWhisper.com Service . such as when you publish your public profile information . becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others without restriction.

VideoWhisper.com may disclose Automatically Collected and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to assist those parties in understanding the usage and demographic patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, or other functionality on the VideoWhisper.com Service.

We may disclose some limited User information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons to: provide web site hosting, maintenance, and security services; fulfill orders; conduct data analysis and create reports; offer certain functionality; and assist VideoWhisper.com in improving the VideoWhisper.com Service and creating new services features. We contractually require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy, we authorize only a limited use of such information, and we require these parties to use reasonable confidentiality measures.

VideoWhisper.com may disclose User information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. copyright or trademark law) or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant in the manner required by the requesting entity.

VideoWhisper.com also reserves the right to disclose User information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; enforce our Terms of Use; protect VideoWhisper.com from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the VideoWhisper.com Service; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of VideoWhisper.com, our Users, or others.

**Data Security**

VideoWhisper.com uses certain physical, managerial, and technical measures designed to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to VideoWhisper.com, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, VideoWhisper.com makes efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If VideoWhisper.com learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. VideoWhisper.com may post a notice on the VideoWhisper.com Service if a security breach occurs.

**Children’s Privacy**

IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE VideoWhisper.com SERVICE AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER.

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, VideoWhisper.com does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 13 years-of-age. If VideoWhisper.com learns that personally-identifiable information of persons less than 13-years-of-age has been collected on or through the VideoWhisper.com Service, then VideoWhisper.com will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who has become VideoWhisper.com Service member, then please contact VideoWhisper.com using our contact links to have that child’s account terminated and information deleted.

The following are some resources that may help parents and legal guardians in monitoring and limiting your children’s' access to certain types of material on the Internet. While VideoWhisper.com does not endorse these products, we provide information about them as a public service to our community.

**Access to your Personal Information**

You may, of course, decline to share your personally-identifiable information with VideoWhisper.com, in which case VideoWhisper.com will not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality found on the VideoWhisper.com Service. You may view, update, correct, or delete your user information and preferences by contacting us from our website.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you account access or making corrections to your information. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR UNIQUE PASSWORD AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL TIMES.

#### **Advertisers and Analytics Providers**

We may use third-party Web analytics services in connection with the VideoWhisper.com Services, such as those of Google Analytics, its advertising features, and Mixpanel. These service providers use a variety of tracking technologies such as cookies to analyze how users use the VideoWhisper.com Services. The information collected (described above in “Automatically Collected Information”) will be collected directly by these service providers to evaluate your use of the VideoWhisper.com Services. For more information on how Google Analytics uses data from our websites and how you can control the information sent to Google, [click here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). To learn about opting out of Google Analytics, please [click here.](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) Because these opt outs are cookie-based, please note that if you get a new computer or device, install or start using a new browser, or erase or alter your browser’s cookie file, you may need to opt out again.

VideoWhisper.com may allow advertisers, third-party advertising networks and third-party advertising serving companies to serve advertisements directly to you within the VideoWhisper.com Services and other VideoWhisper.com sites, services and software. By serving these advertisements directly to you, these companies can set their own cookies on your computer and trigger their own Web beacons and other tracking technologies to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements, and to collect and track information such as demographic information, inferred interests, aggregated information, and activity to assist them in personalizing the advertising content delivered to you. VideoWhisper.com does not provide information that personally identifies you to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, if you respond to an advertisement that targets a certain audience (for example, males age 15 to 18 who have participated in certain promotions), the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience that they were trying to reach.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the tracking technologies and activities of, other advertisers, third-party advertising networks, or third-party advertising servers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these advertisers, third-party advertising networks, or third-party advertising servers. For more information about third-party advertising networks and similar entities that use these technologies, see <http://www.aboutads.info/consumers>, and to opt-out of such ad networks’ and services’ advertising practices, for example, Google Analytics advertising features and Google’s use of cookies, go to the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/%29#completed) page, the [Digital Advertising Alliance opt-out](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) page, or the [Your Online Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices) page.

**In the Event of Merger or Sale**

In the event that VideoWhisper.com is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from Users as part of that merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

**Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically without further notice to you and this will be reflected by the "LAST UPDATED" date found at the top of this page. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when we received that personal information. Your continued use of the VideoWhisper.com Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions.
